{
    "subject": "Brian_Dannelly",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Saved!",
    "human_readable": "Brian Dannelly directed the film Saved!",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8030823469161987,
            "question": "Who directed the film Saved!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7770609855651855,
            "question": "Is Brian Dannelly known for directing other films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7740044593811035,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Brian Dannelly?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7064763903617859,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Brian Dannelly."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38503286242485046,
            "question": "Where was Saved! filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3760053813457489,
            "question": "What is the plot of Saved!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3653172254562378,
            "question": "Is Saved! a comedy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34709659218788147,
            "question": "What genre is the film Saved!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32222962379455566,
            "question": "Who are some of the actors in Saved!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3204018473625183,
            "question": "What year was Saved! released?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Brian Dannelly directed the film Saved!",
            "html": "yago_10556_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of the actors in Saved!",
            "html": "yago_10556_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Saved!",
            "html": "yago_10556_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Saved! a comedy?",
            "html": "yago_10556_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10556_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10556_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10556_164.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10556_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10556_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10556_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10556_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10556_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10556_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_10556_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format with the value as \"yes\" or \"no\":\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the context information contains multiple documents, but all of them describe Brian Dannelly as a film director and screenwriter who worked on the 2004 film Saved!, among other works. This consistently reinforces the idea that Brian Dannelly directed the film Saved!."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Brian Dannelly directed the film Saved!\". Specifically, they mention that Brian Dannelly is an American film director and screenwriter best known for his work on the 2004 film Saved!."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}